Oh, hey! How was your audition?
I'm sorry, do I know you?
What are you doing?
Practicing blowing you off. I'm gonna be a big movie star!
Oh, you got it?
Not yet, but the audition went great!
What's it for?
A big-budget period movie about three Italian brothers...
...who come to America at the turn of the century. It's classy.
The director's supposed to be the next-next Martin Scorsese.
The "next-next"?
A guy from Chicago's supposed to be the next Martin Scorsese.
This guy's right after him.
Hello?
Joey, it's Estelle. I just talked to the casting people. They loved you!
They loved me!
They want to see you again tomorrow.
Oh, my God.
Just one thing.
Do you have a problem with full-frontal nudity?
Are you kidding me? I never rent a movie without it!
Oh.
Uh, okay, let me call you back.
What's the matter?
They want me naked in the movie.
Wow.     -I know.
My grandmother's gonna see this.
Grandma's gonna have to get in line.
The wedding's so close. Are you nervous?
Yeah, but I also can't wait till it's over.
We have a pact not to have sex again until the wedding.
A "no sex" pact, huh?
I have one of those with every woman in America.
Will you give me a hand making up the guest bedroom?
Cousin Cassie's staying with us for a few days.
Cassie? I haven't seen her in, like, forever.
I wonder if she still carries a Barbie everywhere?
She's 25 years old.
So? I still...
You're probably right.
Hi.
Hey.
Pheebs, can I talk to you over here for a second?
Yeah.
Subtle, guys.
What?
I know you're planning my surprise bridal shower.
Ha, okay, well, don't ruin it. Just play along, at least.
Okay. Sorry.
Okay.
Oh, my God. We have to throw her a shower?
What'd you decide to do about the movie?
I don't know.
It's not like it's porn. This is a serious, legitimate movie.
Nudity's really important to the story.
That's what you say about porn.
Maybe I shouldn't go on the callback.
No, you should. A lot of major actors do nude scenes.
The chance to star in a movie? Come on!
That's true. And I'm only naked in one scene. It sounds really great.
My character's Catholic. He falls in love with a Jewish girl.
We run away and get caught in a big rainstorm.
We go into a barn, undress each other and hold each other.
It's really sweet and tender.
Plus, everyone is gonna see your thing.
When can we have this shower?
She has so much going on, we have only two options.
We have Friday.
That's just two days away.
What is the other option?
Yesterday.
Well, if we make it yesterday, woo-hoo, we're done.
It's impossible. We can't do this by Friday.
We have to find a place, invite people, get food.
There's too much to do.
We cannot do it!
Calm down!
Okay. I'm sorry, you're right. I'm sorry.
Just calm down, woman!
Phoebe, I already did.
All right, then I need to calm down.
Okay.
I think we can do this if we just get organized.
Uh-huh.
We have two days to plan this party.
We just need to make fast decisions.
Mm-hm.
Where will we have it?
Um, here. What time?
Four o'clock. Food?
Finger sandwiches and tea.
Ooh, great. Very Monica.
And chili.
Ah, you went one too far.
Uh, flowers or balloons?
Both.
We're paying for this. Okay.
Neither.
Um, what should we do for the theme?
"Lusts of the Flesh."
What?
I don't know. Cowboy theme?
Hey.
I'm glad we decided not to sleep together before the wedding.
Oh, boy. Me too.
You know, I was thinking, if we had a big fight...
Mm-hm. ...and, uh, we broke up for a few hours.
Yeah.
Technically, we could have sex again.
What do you think, bossy and domineering?
The wedding's off, sloppy and immature.
That's me. Come on.
Okay.
Wait. Cassie's in the guest room. We're going to lunch.
Get rid of her, obsessive and shrill!
Shrill? The wedding is back on.
I thought I heard voices. You must be Chandler.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
So, ready to go?
Yeah.
Chandler?
I'll be right with you.
Cassie needs to stay at your place.
Why?
Because "Pervie Perverson" here can't stop staring at her.
Chandler, she's our cousin!
I wasn't staring. I was listening intently.
It's called being a good conversationalist. Watch.
Say something.
You were staring about eight inches south of there.
Fine. She can stay at my place.
What does Cassie look like now?
She looks exactly like Aunt Marilyn.
Huh.
So this Aunt Marilyn, is she coming to the wedding?
Wafer-thin ice.
Hey, I'm back.
Hi, Joey.
Uh, so, will I be reading the same scene again?
I tried to call you. You didn't need to come today.
Oh, great.
I'd have been perfect for this part.
You made a bad decision and ruined your movie. Good day!
You didn't need to come, because the director saw your tape and loved it.
And scene.
Huh? Wasn't that fun?
We did a little improv there. Yeah!
So, you... You were saying?
The director wants to meet you tomorrow.
Wow. Sure. That's great.
Your agent said you're okay with nudity.
Yeah, sure. As long as it's handled tastefully.
And that barn is not too cold.
Terrific. Well, uh, there's one more thing.
Uh... Uh, it's important to the director that everything in the movie is authentic.
In your love scene with Sarah...
...she talks about how she's never seen a naked man who wasn't Jewish.
So...
So, what?
So, uh, well, the director is insisting that whoever play that part...
...be authentically, uh, anatomically...
...not Jewish. You know what I'm saying?
Yes!
No. What?
An Italian Catholic immigrant at this time would not be...
Bar mitzvah-ed?
To get this part, you can't be...
No.
But you are?
Yep.
You told them you weren't?
That's right.
Wow. Wow.
It's definitely all gone? There's nothing there to work with?
What were you thinking?
I don't know. I just want this part.
They say no matter what you're asked during an audition, say yes.
They want you to ride a horse, say you can.
You figure out how to do it later.
This is not like learning to ride a horse. This is like learning to...
...grow a turtleneck.
I know, okay? Tomorrow, when I go meet the director...
...I have to take my clothes off so they can see what my body looks like.
Oh, my God. What are you gonna do?
I have to call my agent and tell her I can't do the part.
Unless...
Unless what?
This may sound crazy, but there may be something we could...
...fashion.
Like what?
Well, I'm not sure yet, but, um...
...off the top of my head, I'm thinking...
...double-sided tape and some sort of luncheon meat.
I've got a great idea for party favors for the shower.
We get mahogany boxes and carve everyone's names in them.
Then inside is each person's individual birthstone.
Okay. Okay.
All right, you take care of that.
Okay.
Meanwhile, the party's tomorrow and we don't have a guest list.
Okay. Who do we know that's coming? Me. Are you?
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
I'm making something for Joey. Can I raid your fridge?
Have at it.
All right. Turkey? Mm, that won't work.
Cheese? That won't work.
Olive loaf? I hope that won't work.
Are you making him a sandwich?
No, it's, um, more like a wrap.
Okay, so, um, I'm gonna go, guys.
So you can get back to deciding on what to get me for a present!
We have to get her a present?
Okay, but look. Look at what I got.
It's her address book. We have a guest list.
Ah.
You're amazing. Did you pull that out of her purse?
Uh-huh. And a little seed money for the party.
Oh, nice.
Cassie?
Hey, Ross.
Hi. Ha, ha.
It's been so long!
Last time I saw you...
...you were setting up your tent in line for Return of the Jedi.
Oh, uh, that's right.
So you did see me that day. Because it seemed like you didn't.
Yeah, sorry about that.
It's okay. Come on in.
Thanks for letting me stay here. Monica's place was nice.
But her fiancé sure stares a lot.
Oh.
Oh, my God! You do a great Chandler!
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I have a knack for impressions.
Well, maybe after we get re-acquainted, uh, you could do me.
Yeah. No!
Cassie, how you...? How you doing on that...
...hot dog?
I'm all done.
Thank God.
The last time we hung out was when our parents rented that beach house.
Oh, right, right. Ooh, remember the time...
...l, uh, pinned you down and tickled you until you cried?
We're probably too old to do that now.
I'll always remember that summer. It's when I got all these freckles.
Uh-huh, Uh-huh.
And... And I'll always remember that summer...
...because that's when I realized that we are related.
It took you that long to figure it out, huh?
Um, I'm a little slow.
Just as our children would be.
Hi.
How are you? Good. Hi. Thanks for coming.
Oh, thank you.
Thank you. So nice to see you.
No, thanks.
Okay. Hey, Rach?
Yeah?
Who the hell are all these people?
I don't know. I called everybody in her book.
These are the ones that could show up on 24 hours' notice.
There's a word for people like that: Losers.
Hi, I'm Rachel. This is Phoebe. I'm the maid of honor.
How do you know Monica?
I was her accountant four years ago.
Oh...
I'm interested to find out who's been doing her taxes the last four years.
That's great.
When is Monica supposed to get here?
I don't know.
Excuse us.
You didn't tell her?
You were supposed to.
You were supposed to tell her to come! I was bringing the cake!
Fine, I'll go call her.
And please tell her to bring a cake!
We have a lot of options. A number of prototypes for you to try on.
Wow, those look great.
Okay, this one's a mushroom cap. Uh, this one is made of bologna.
And... And the toothpicks?
Just until the glue dries.
Thank God.
These are more realistic, but perishable.
Over here, we have pink suede, which is nice.
But if it gets wet, it'll shrink.
Maybe we'll just take that one away.
I also did a little something in fur, but, uh, that's really just for me.
Why don't you try these on? We'll get a better idea of what works.
Thanks, you are such a good friend. And this is so weird.
Ow.
Toothpick?
Yeah.
What are you trying now?
The Fruit Roll-up.
And?
Delicious.
Joey.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. We have a winner!
What? Which one?
The Silly Putty. Not so silly anymore!
She's your cousin. She's your cousin.
If she knew what was going on in your head, she'd think you were sick.
Or would she? Let's back up for a second.
She was the one who suggested opening a bottle of wine.
She was the one who turned down the lights.
She was the one that wanted to rent Logan's Run...
...the sexiest movie ever.
I know that look.
Forget it. I want it. She wants it.
I'm going in.
What the hell are you doing?
Say something clever.
Okay, doesn't have to be clever.
Just has to be words. Say some words.
Any words will do.
Oh, my God, this is the longest...
...that anyone has not talked ever!
There is nothing you could say to make this worse...
...so just say something!
I haven't had sex in a very long time.
Yeah, you really shouldn't have said anything.
Phoebe? Rachel? It's Monica.
I wonder what you could possibly need me for on such short notice?
Oh.
Oh, Monica. We are so sorry.
For what?
First, for forgetting to throw you a bridal shower.
Then, forgetting to invite you to it.
You already had it?
We called everyone in your phone book. A bunch of people came.
It took us so long to get you here that they had to leave.
We wanted to throw you a big surprise and a great shower.
Now you don't have either.
We ruined everything.
Ugh.
No, wait a minute, that's not true. What you did was really sweet.
It kind of works out for the best, heh.
What do you mean?
Now I get to spend my shower with the only people I really love.
I get all those presents without talking to people I don't even like!
Surprise.
Surprise, Monica.
What's cool is, the character is from Naples, right?
Yeah.
My whole family's from Naples.
That's great. Okay. I've heard everything I need to hear...
We just need to, uh...
Leslie?
Uh, Joey, this is the awkward part.
Oh, hey, right. Not a problem.
I totally understand you need to...
...make sure I don't have any horrible scars or tattoos.
Don't you worry.
I have nothing to hide.
So, there you go. That's me.
One hundred-percent natural.
I tell you, that has never happened before.
Cassie, are you finding everything okay?
Yeah. Thank you so much for letting me stay here.
Oh, it's no problem. I've...
What?
Say something. Say anything.
Ask her out! She's not your cousin!